<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rich People Quotes</string>
    <string-array name="text">

        <item>If you want to get rich, remember that the way to do it is via equity, not salary.</item>

        <item>No wealth can ever make a bad man at peace with himself.</item>

        <item>There are a great many people accumulating what they think is vast wealth, but it’s only money.</item>

        <item>It’s simple arithmetic: “Your income can grow only to the extent you do”.</item>
        <item>The individual investor should act consistently as an investor and not as a speculator.</item>

        <item>Wealth does not make people happy, but positive increases in wealth may.</item>

        <item>99% of all problems can be solved by money — and for the other </item>

        <item>The fools in life want things fast and easy — money, success, attention.</item>

        <item>It’s amazing how fast later comes when you buy now.</item>

        <item>Remember that the only purpose of money is to get you what you want, so think hard about what you value and put it above money.</item>


        <item>Wealth after all is a relative thing since he that has little and wants less is richer than he that has much and wants more.</item>


        <item>A sign of wealth: No longer needing an alarm clock to wake up.</item>


        <item>Within certain limits, it is actually true that the less money you have, the less you worry.</item>


        <item>The four most expensive words in the English language are, ‘This time it’s different.’</item>

        <item>Be careful to leave your sons well instructed rather than rich, for the hopes of the instructed are better than the wealth of the ignorant.</item>


        <item>Money grows on the tree of persistence.</item>

        <item>The more you learn, the more you earn.</item>


        <item>I think everybody should get rich and famous and do everything they ever dreamed of so they can see that it’s not the answer.</item>


        <item>Real wealth is not about money. Real wealth is: not having to go to meetings, not having to spend time with jerks, not being locked into status games, not feeling like you have to say “yes”, not worrying about others claiming your time and energy. Real wealth is about freedom.</item>


        <item>Motivational Saving Money Quotes</item>


        <item>Wealth consists not in having great possessions, but in having few wants.</item>


        <item>How many millionaires do you know who have become wealthy by investing in savings accounts? I rest my case.</item>


        <item>So many people of wealth understand much more about making and saving money than about using and enjoying it. They fail to live because they are always preparing to live.</item>


        <item>Stop buying things you don’t need, to impress people you don’t even like.</item>


        <item>Wealth is not his that has it, but his that enjoys it.</item>


        <item>You must gain control over your money or the lack of it will forever control you.</item>


        <item>A sign of wealth: No longer needing an alarm clock to wake up.</item>


        <item>Within certain limits, it is actually true that the less money you have, the less you worry.</item>


        <item>The four most expensive words in the English language are, ‘This time it’s different.’</item>

        <item>Be careful to leave your sons well instructed rather than rich, for the hopes of the instructed are better than the wealth of the ignorant.</item>


        <item>Money grows on the tree of persistence.</item>

        <item>The more you learn, the more you earn.</item>


        <item>I think everybody should get rich and famous and do everything they ever dreamed of so they can see that it’s not the answer.</item>


        <item>Real wealth is not about money. Real wealth is: not having to go to meetings, not having to spend time with jerks, not being locked into status games, not feeling like you have to say “yes”, not worrying about others claiming your time and energy. Real wealth is about freedom.</item>


        <item>Motivational Saving Money Quotes</item>

        <item>It’s simple arithmetic: “Your income can grow only to the extent you do”.</item>
        <item>The individual investor should act consistently as an investor and not as a speculator.</item>

        <item>Wealth does not make people happy, but positive increases in wealth may.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>